[Music]
foreign
automation tutorial
so I already published two lessons
covering how to download and install
Tasker latest version 16 and also I've
explained you the navigation of your
Tasker
so this is our lesson three where I'm
gonna teach you how to create the
workspace
in present is task
please do subscribe to the channel click
on Bell icon you'll receive
notifications whenever I publish more
videos
thank you
okay so to create the workspace first
you need to download the automation
specialist level one base dot TSU file
okay this is actually a file which
contains pre-created artifacts which
will be relevant for your
lessons so I'm gonna teach you
automation Concepts in the next sessions
right so this dot TSU file is necessary
for you to understand the concepts so
first you need to download that file
and then
to create a workspace you need to select
a repository what kind of repository
what type of repository you want to
create
and then you are going to provide the
name of your new new workspace
and use workspace template by selecting
the dot TSU file that you have
downloaded
and then click on create
okay so these are the high level steps
that
uh steps that you need to follow to
create the workspace okay now let's jump
onto the system and let's create the
workflow in presenters.com
okay so this is my task okay how to
create workspace let's see now uh by
using actual Tasker tool okay so all you
need to do is first you need to click on
create new button okay
and then here first you need to select
the type of Repository so there are
different types of repositories but for
this session we are gonna select as none
which creates a single user workspace
and then you need to select
a
new workspace location where you would
like to store your entire
workspace data right so I want to keep
this as default okay and then you need
to select the name of your new workspace
okay
YouTube uh probably like
project
e-commerce
okay
and then
you have to check use workspace template
okay so as I told you earlier you have
to download the
automation specialist level one base TSU
file
before you create workspace so this file
is being provided by by try sentence
Tasker whenever you install your Tasker
version 16. okay so this base TSU will
be coming along with your installation
okay
so now
all you need to do here select use
workspace template and browse your
workspace template thus that we have
downloaded just now what is this
automation specialist level 1 base TSU
Okay click on open
and then click on OK
so it will take a couple of seconds to
create your entire workspace by using
the base
TSU file that we have attached while
creating the workspace
okay so that base TSU will have your
predefined
objects and predefined modules okay so
if you see here so the new project has
been created and you see you already
have some predefined modules if you see
here modules see standard module and
then you have Workshop module okay under
work workshop module you have all these
modules are the objects that are already
added
in the workspace C everything is added
all the modules and the locators are
added okay so that the advantage of your
base TSU okay automation specialist
level 1 base TSU hope you understand how
to create the workspace by using Tasker
version 16. okay if you have any queries
you can leave your comments in the
comment box I'll try to respond to your
queries
hope you all understand the concept of
creation of the workspace by using
Tasker
please do subscribe to the channel click
on Bell icon you'll receive
notifications more videos thank you
[Music]